Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org
You're a Hunter.
I am Elle.
I know. I love you and all.
You don't have to sell yourself
me.
I gave up my room.
It's a shame.
The airline lost my luggage due to the fog.
It's been a disaster.
Aren't you the poor little match girl?
Hans Christian Andersen.
I don't really listen to European music.
I'm so excited to be in the movie with you.
Shit.
My room looks like this.
Hey.
You know I can stay on the couch.
It looks super comfortable.
You can stay with me.
I'm removing my face.
Well.
Cool.
I don't know if I can publish them.
People will say I've become... inaccessible.
Can you help me with this?
You have expensive tastes.
A date to play?
That bracelet hasn't been in fashion for centuries.
It's for the masses.
For the masses?
Oh. you're so hard to understand.
That.
Who would want to be someone people can relate to?
A hunter wants to be approachable and understanding.
It's a matter of metrics.
Oh. no. no. no.
You can let the numbers measure you. but you can't measure yourself by the numbers.
That's wise.
Did you learn it in a sound bath session?
There is not a single person on this planet like you.
You are a very specific speck of stardust.
Arrest.
No. you stop.
This means something.
Say it with me.
Am
a completely unique consciousness.
I am a saint.
unique consciousness.
And I am made of stardust.
Am
made of stardust.
The moment you forget that. is the moment you disappear.
I'm sorry. but who are you?
I'd like to introduce you to Dominique.
my stepmother.
But you're so young.
and you know nothing
about Johnny Thunders.
one of my fathers.
She likes beautiful things and beautiful people.
He is a powerful man.
If you think he's playing with you.
he is.
If you think he's being honest with you.
Sometimes he wants to impress you.
Other times he wants to be impressed by you. usually the latter.
In his opinion. you either have it or you don't.
It must be genetic. because I'm the same.
You pricked me.
Oh dear.
Very sorry.
Isn't that a sign of good luck?
In fact. it is.
A needle prick is a sign of success.
Damn. you bastard.
Preferably in the eye.
Have you ever experienced any misfortune?
I am a victim of the fog.
It's not the fog that you should be worried about.
That's what fog brings.
It's a tragedy. in my opinion.
Something no parent should have to endure.
I remember the day you were born.
The day I saw the universe.
My dear Al.
I will always carry you with me.
Always.
I couldn't imagine losing you.
But if I did. I would travel the earth until my legs stopped working.
And if I had to kill to find you. I would. and I would keep doing it.
I would dye the oceans red before I would give you up.
And so.
my dear girls.
It is the tragedy of the Leather Man.
WHO?
The leather man is...
a father
searching for his lost daughter in the underworld.
A father condemned to search for lifetimes
who eventually forgets who they are looking for.
But when the fog returns
He remembers it.
He remembers her.
He comes with the fog
Search
her face and
infinite abyss
its strength
Unbeatable. he wears leather gloves covered in razor-sharp diamonds.
Looking for her and any girl who sees him. for when you see him.
He sees his daughter and will try to...
Destroying you and anyone around you to reach her. and the only way to kill you
His hands must be cut off.
That's why they say.
Take care of your daughters. or he will.
Dad is fascinating.
He's just a money man. and you can call him Johnny.
I didn't expect Johnny to be like that at all.
He is very curious and protective.
It has this reversed logic where he
thinks that sleeping with girls my age will somehow bring
He's closer to me.
But didn't he marry Dominique?
Why are you leaving me. Dad?
I want you and Dominique to be friends again.
It's a sweet fantasy.
You know. making a movie is like going to war.
This will bring your daughters closer together.
I'm here because I wanted to go to war with you.
I would never have agreed to this if I had known you were going to go.
If I stay. I'll only prevent you two from reconciling.
The fact that you girls are getting together is how we become a family again.
Dominic is one of us.
She's like us. but she's not one of us.
There is a difference.
She loves you madly.
Perhaps more than he loves me.
This movie is going to be hell.
Promise me you'll behave and play nice while I'm gone.
What is he doing?
Just kill me. I am
I'm sorry. but do you want to hear something?
Last night I immersed myself in the world of Leatherman.
And everything Johnny said is true.
And there are
these beings
called the kingmakers.
This pair of women always come in pairs.
And they can
to be old or young.
horrible or beautiful.
And sometimes.
They can even
They become shapeshifting foxes with multiple tails.
Magic foxes?
Yeah.
And they are the guides for the Leatherman.
And they are neither good nor bad.
Neutral.
Morally ambiguous.
This type of leather is genuine.
It has always existed; some cultures call it leather.
king but
Most people call
he the
devil
and
These are magical
Foxes that
help him find his destroyer.
They're the ones who do it.
And they are the ones who finish him off!
I just want you to understand.
that what we saw was not a normal murder.
What the hell is a normal murder?
I think you two should be a little more traumatized by this.
Trauma comes in many forms.
I mean.
Today I couldn't even pretend to kill Elle.
We saw the Leatherman.
Elle. I'm so sorry to miss your big day tomorrow.
But I'm glad we can make peace.
Use it with love. Dad.
I saw the Leatherman.
I saw him take my daughter away.
Is it a ghost?
A monster?
A god?
I don't know. but what I do
All I know is that the fog has returned.
The girls are dying.
I will never stop looking for her.
Yankee.
Welcome.
Soldier K.
It's been a long time.
I thought you had already left.
Not yet. but perhaps soon.
Is that so.
This is the latest version.
I can't stand it.
I read it this morning.
I'm sure your daughter will like it.
I would like to buy this.
Thank you.
Who is he?
The saddest person in the world.
That person is a soldier in the United States.
Her name is Kei-san.
He brought his daughter here.
But she was kidnapped.
One of the kidnapped girls.
The other day. when that fog came out...
One of the girls you heard about?
You're one of them. aren't you?
Some say it's the work of monsters.
They say it's the work of monsters from that world.
There are many ghosts around us.
But everything that happens to them is the work of humans.
Thank you so much.
Come
Hello.
People tell me I want to die.
I've thought about it.
I thought that if I died. I would go to hell.
If I went to hell. I could find the leather.
If I find him.
He could kill him.
I still can't do that.
Not now.
Hell.
That...?
He!
Oh
I screwed up this time.
I understand your situation.
Losing a child the way you lost him.
Well. the Yakuza is one thing. but our friends in the police department.
they cannot have the
Men confuse mercy with weakness.
You couldn't protect your family. that's why you're so focused on this.
It's karma.
Courtesy of Uncle San.
Dad.
It's not the fog that should worry you.
That's what fog brings.
When the fog returns. he remembers.
Dad!
And she will destroy everything and everyone in her path to reach her.
Take care of your daughters. or he will.
It's a bit theatrical. but it's tradition.
Hmm.
That's great.
You speak like wolves.
We used to talk about it all the time.
It's our secret language.
Know...
When I met Al. she told me she was an orphan.
So I bought her drinks all night.
My little match girl.
She got so drunk that I had to take her home.
He vomited everywhere. on me and on my bed.
And we have loved each other ever since.
I want to be an orphan too.
Should we play orphans tonight?
Nico is in town.
He would probably adopt us all.
Tea?
Nico?
Put your tongue back in your mouth.
Oh. please!
I adore Nico.
And he's always wanted to meet you.
Of course he wants to meet me.
It is well known that he hates my father.
I read it.
I gave our driver the night off.
I don't need one of my husband's snitches watching us.
I'm going home.
Do you really want the night to end?
You're fucking evil.
Johnny Thunders is a sick son of a bitch.
Hello.
Like strange things.
Well?
Like a real piece of shit weirdo.
But Johnny.
He's on another level.
We were at this lesbian event of the day and then at the performance.
The truth is that it was quite interesting.
A crowd of filthy shit.
And at the heart of all this.
Johnny was there.
And Johnny was pointing directly at me.
Like. right in front of me.
Do you want to see something scary?
The next thing I know is that...
I'm in this art studio behind a dumpling shop in Chinatown.
Viewing a Super 8 installation.
about one of the greatest living artists. tattooed on a skull.
in a damned fetus.
How disgusting! Like a baby?
Like a dead baby. yes.
Did Johnny see this?
Oh yes. he bought it right there.
I paid about $10.000 for it. in cash.
Do you know anything about this?
Have you seen the fetus?
My father protects me.
Well. aren't you Daddy's little baby?
I could even tell you how you can't keep your hands off my stepmother.
Hunter. what is that terrifying thing you want to tell me?
Oh my God. it was terrifying!
Have you heard of the Leather Men?
That?
The Leather Man.
Death has its time.
My daughter didn't receive a single second more than what she was entitled to.
If I could take the pain away from her. I would.
The bodies blame time.
Memories distort time.
But I know that time promises to love. and only love.
Yoko is not here tonight.
These have been difficult times for you. soldier K.
We know that your heart has been darkened by grief.
Most people choose to live in a
A tolerable amount of pain.
But you. Soldier K.
You have chosen to live in agony.
You are just a memory you can't let go of.
It won't work for us.
We know your daughter is a strong girl.
A resilient person.
His will alone has kept your blood warm.
Throughout all these years. we
You should know that she is not far from you.
She is in her kingdom.
his kingdom in the mist.
and the fog is right in front of you.
The Leatherman must die.
And then. and only then. will you see your daughter.
I remember when I
He came to catch a ghost.
You must become a ghost.
a gift from my puppy.
I know this isn't going to work.
What's not going to work?
This movie isn't going to fix us.
I don't have any wrong ideas about how to fix things.
I don't love you so that you will love me.
I just do it.
Christ.
That girl is fucking unbearable.
She's really begging to be touched.
Imagine being so attractive but at the same time so impossible to fuck.
Oh.
Are you evil?
I slept with Nico the other night.
That's vile.
Opposite.
It tasted like soap.
In some ways. it's even worse.
I kind of like its taste.
Does Johnny know?
Your father and I enjoy our secrets.
It's part of our contract.
But we didn't lie.
Not among them.
And no one else.
Except for that one time.
Do you feel like I've replaced you?
you.
No one could replace you. Elle.
Neither him nor me.
Did you think that getting married
Would my father bring me closer to you?
That's one way to look at it.
Perhaps that was part of it
Perhaps becoming friends again is unattainable.
I will always be your wicked stepmother.
This family is rotten.
I should probably save her from him.
Or he of her.
You can leave.
I can distract Nico.
Niko says that nothing spontaneous happens in these places.
private parties and we should go to the uniform
evening.
What happens on uniform night?
Nobody!
I missed you.
I'm not in the mood.
Dad.
Can you taste it?
Can you taste it? Can you taste the soap?
Your friends are going to love this.
Oh yeah? You're going to tell me.
You're going to be a little gossip!
Elle. I don't love you.
There is nothing you want or have that does not belong to me.
You will never be one of us.
You are just a possession. something worn out. dry.
used thing that my father will fuck
throw away.
Toxic shit waste.
You think you are very special.
For some reason. everyone else seems to think the same. but I see you.
I used to think we were the same. but I don't let myself be guided by doubt or self-pity.
I do not pity my father.
I write my own story.
I have reinvented myself.
I used to wonder how it was possible
someone who had everything going for him to be so cruel and insecure.
And then I met you. and I had never met anyone so empty and disappointing.
You're not going home until you've worn my skin!
Money isn't going to solve this. damn it!
And life won't fix it!
My dad's not going to fix it!
Your dad?
You know. the other day. after your dad fucked me. he confessed something to me.
She told me how painful it was.
How disgusting it is to come face to face with
-to face all the things he hates most about himself and you.
He looks at you and all he sees is an open mouth of misery and need.
It doesn't surprise me that he's always leaving.
He can't stand you for a second.
Shit!
Damned psychopath.
Go to hell. bitch!
Don't bring a knife to an ass fight. you fucking bitch!
We don't usually do that.
We have the opportunity to choose our destiny.
But you've always been special.
She.
After all.
The needle of success pricked you.
If you put on these gloves.
You will find what you have lost.
FRENCH BRAKE
Do you want subtitles for any video?
-=[ ai.OpenSubtitles.com ]=-